Toggle navigation [WinningPrizeSearch.com](http://www.winningprizesearch.com/)

September 17th, 2024

[**Click Here to Sign Up**](http://www.winningprizesearch.com/registration_page.php) and get the BEST handpicked, winnable sweepstakes and bonus prizes delivered to your mailbox!

**Privacy Policy**

WinningPrizeSearch.com understands the importance of protecting personal privacy and is committed to protecting users privacy. When advertising orders are placed, WinningPrizeSearch.com uses the information from users to correctly process orders and to improve our ability to understand our user's needs. WinningPrizeSearch.com policy applies only to WinningPrizeSearch.com. Orders are processed securely by Avangate.Com, and their complete privacy policy can be viewed at www.avangate.com.

**Description of Information Collected and Usage**

WinningPrizeSearch.com stores any information provided by a user. When a user makes a purchase, except for credit card details, information supplied on the purchase order is passed to WinningPrizeSearch.com. This information may be used to notify the user automatically of product updates, upgrades, new products, support and/or special pricing offers on future products.

Orders are handled through Avangate.Com and their complete privacy policy can be seen from their website at www.avangate.com. When an order is processed, except for credit card details, information supplied on the purchase order form is passed through to WinningPrizeSearch.com from Avangate.Com. No credit card details (credit card number, expiry date) is ever seen, received or stored by WinningPrizeSearch.com.

WinningPrizeSearch.com also reserves the right to provide aggregate information about site usage and traffic patterns, stripped of any individual identification, to third parties for marketing research.

**Information Collected for Internal Feedback**

WinningPrizeSearch.com reserves the right to use the data collected and use it for market research purposes in order to improve WinningPrizeSearch.com user service and products.

**Policies Regarding Third Parties**

Orders are processed securely by Avangate.Com, and their privacy policy can be viewed on their website at www.avangate.com.

WinningPrizeSearch.com current policy is to not sell, rent or trade personal information to others; however, WinningPrizeSearch.com reserves the right to do so in the future.

Users with concerns about disclosing personal information may send an e-mail to techsupport, at WinningPrizeSearch.com.com, and your information will remain private. In this email, users should include a current email address and the words "remain private" in the subject field.

**Third Party Advertising Vendors**

* Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website or other websites.
* Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
* Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting Ads Settings. (Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting www.aboutads.info.)

**WinningPrizeSearch.com Privacy Policy Changes**

If WinningPrizeSearch.com decides to change its privacy policy, WinningPrizeSearch.com will post these changes here. Please feel free to contact WinningPrizeSearch.com to our techsupport, at WinningPrizeSearch.com if you have further questions regarding our privacy policy.
